[
    {
        "Question": "assertion",
        "Answer": "claim",
        "Options": "declaration/ statement"
    },
    {
        "Question": "assessed",
        "Answer": "evaluated",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "asset",
        "Answer": "advantage",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "assimilated",
        "Answer": "absorbed",
        "Options": "combined"
    },
    {
        "Question": "assistance",
        "Answer": "help",
        "Options": "aid"
    },
    {
        "Question": "associates",
        "Answer": "connects",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "assorted",
        "Answer": "various",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "assume",
        "Answer": "believe",
        "Options": "suppose"
    },
    {
        "Question": "assured",
        "Answer": "guaranteed",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "astonishing",
        "Answer": "incredible",
        "Options": "amazing/ surprising"
    },
    {
        "Question": "astoundingly",
        "Answer": "incredibly",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "astute",
        "Answer": "clever",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "at random",
        "Answer": "without a definite pattern",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "attachment to",
        "Answer": "preference to",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "attain",
        "Answer": "achieve",
        "Options": "reach"
    },
    {
        "Question": "attendant",
        "Answer": "accompanying",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "attest",
        "Answer": "confirm",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "attributes",
        "Answer": "ascribes/ credited",
        "Options": "characteristics/ properties"
    },
    {
        "Question": "augment",
        "Answer": "increase",
        "Options": "supplement"
    },
    {
        "Question": "authenticity",
        "Answer": "genineness",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "authoritative",
        "Answer": "official",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "autonomy",
        "Answer": "independence",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "aware of",
        "Answer": "familiar with",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "a wealth of",
        "Answer": "an abundance of",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "available",
        "Answer": "obtainable",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "avenue",
        "Answer": "means",
        "Options": "methods"
    },
    {
        "Question": "avid",
        "Answer": "enthusiasitc",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "back up",
        "Answer": "support",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "barely",
        "Answer": "just",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "barren",
        "Answer": "infertile",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "barrier",
        "Answer": "impediment",
        "Options": "obstacle"
    },
    {
        "Question": "beforehand",
        "Answer": "foreordain",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "beckon",
        "Answer": "invite",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "being a drain on the tree",
        "Answer": "wasting the treeâ€™s resources",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "beneficial",
        "Answer": "helpful",
        "Options": "advantageous"
    },
    {
        "Question": "besides",
        "Answer": "in addition to",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "bias",
        "Answer": "prejudice",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "bizarre",
        "Answer": "odd",
        "Options": "very strange"
    },
    {
        "Question": "blossom",
        "Answer": "flourish",
        "Options": "thrive"
    },
    {
        "Question": "boast",
        "Answer": "exaggerate",
        "Options": "puff"
    },
    {
        "Question": "bombard",
        "Answer": "strike",
        "Options": "assault"
    },
    {
        "Question": "boom",
        "Answer": "expansion",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "boost",
        "Answer": "raise",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "boundary",
        "Answer": "periphery",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "branch",
        "Answer": "division",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "breed",
        "Answer": "reproduce",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "brew",
        "Answer": "develop",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "brilliant",
        "Answer": "bright",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "brittle",
        "Answer": "breakable",
        "Options": "fragile"
    },
    {
        "Question": "bulk",
        "Answer": "mass",
        "Options": "largest part"
    },
    {
        "Question": "burdensome",
        "Answer": "difficult",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "burgeon",
        "Answer": "expand",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "bustling",
        "Answer": "busy",
        "Options": "lively"
    },
    {
        "Question": "by and large",
        "Answer": "for the most part",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "camouflage",
        "Answer": "disguise/ decorate",
        "Options": "blend with background"
    },
    {
        "Question": "capacity",
        "Answer": "available storage space",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "cardinal",
        "Answer": "fundamental",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "carried on",
        "Answer": "continued",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "casts off",
        "Answer": "gets rid of",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "catastrophic",
        "Answer": "extremely harmful",
        "Options": "disastrous"
    },
    {
        "Question": "ceased",
        "Answer": "stopped",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "celebrated",
        "Answer": "famous",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "central",
        "Answer": "essential",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "championed",
        "Answer": "supported",
        "Options": "promoted"
    },
    {
        "Question": "chancy",
        "Answer": "risky",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "channel",
        "Answer": "direct",
        "Options": "guide"
    },
    {
        "Question": "chaotic",
        "Answer": "disorganized",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "cherish",
        "Answer": "value",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "chief",
        "Answer": "major",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "chisel",
        "Answer": "carve",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "choose",
        "Answer": "select",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "chronic",
        "Answer": "inveterate",
        "Options": "habitual/ persistent"
    },
    {
        "Question": "chronology",
        "Answer": "a list that pairs events with dates",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "circumstances",
        "Answer": "conditions",
        "Options": "situation"
    },
    {
        "Question": "cited",
        "Answer": "mentioned",
        "Options": "quoted/ referred to"
    },
    {
        "Question": "classic",
        "Answer": "typical",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "clear",
        "Answer": "visible",
        "Options": "apparrent"
    },
    {
        "Question": "cling to",
        "Answer": "attach",
        "Options": "hold on"
    },
    {
        "Question": "close",
        "Answer": "careful",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "clues",
        "Answer": "information",
        "Options": "hints"
    },
    {
        "Question": "cluster",
        "Answer": "group",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "coalesced",
        "Answer": "joined",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "coated",
        "Answer": "layer",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "collaborate",
        "Answer": "work together/ cooperate",
        "Options": "join together"
    },
    {
        "Question": "collective",
        "Answer": "group",
        "Options": "gather"
    },
    {
        "Question": "collide with",
        "Answer": "run into",
        "Options": "hit each other"
    },
    {
        "Question": "colossal",
        "Answer": "enormous",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "coinage",
        "Answer": "creation",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "coincides with",
        "Answer": "occurs at the same time as",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "comes close",
        "Answer": "approaches",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "commemorate",
        "Answer": "celebrate",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "commence",
        "Answer": "begin",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "commonly",
        "Answer": "often",
        "Options": "generally/ normally"
    },
    {
        "Question": "compacted",
        "Answer": "compressed",
        "Options": "concise"
    },
    {
        "Question": "comparably",
        "Answer": "similarly",
        "Options": "equivalently"
    },
    {
        "Question": "comparative",
        "Answer": "relative",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "compatible",
        "Answer": "equivalent",
        "Options": "consistent"
    },
    {
        "Question": "compelled",
        "Answer": "required",
        "Options": "push"
    },
    {
        "Question": "compelling",
        "Answer": "persuasive/ convincing",
        "Options": "forcing"
    },
    {
        "Question": "compensates for",
        "Answer": "makes up for",
        "Options": "reimburse"
    }
]